{
    "id": "df5e1f1dc2974be1b3cf2f28af31f35c",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We commenced work ………………… Monday.",
            "description": "From indicates some point of time. It is used with all tenses.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "in",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0fabb22017504f35a020a8d58150c330"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat …………………….. a chair.",
            "description": "We use on to speak of things at rest.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "onto"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b4eee04b4514e26b7ef1f28125ad12c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I slept ……………………… 11 o’clock.",
            "description": "We use till to indicate time. We use up to to indicate distance or quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "until",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45296c42e93b44b9840a21c3acf5d21c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not eaten anything ……………………… yesterday.",
            "description": "Since denotes some point of time in the past. It is used with a perfect tense.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "882abaaecb9346209311c028aa341535"
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked …………………………. the end of the street.",
            "description": "We use up to to talk about distance.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c8e01080fb1846aa8ee54b5011fd4fb9"
        },
        {
            "question": "An old feud existed ………………………. the two families.",
            "description": "We use between to speak of two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bebe87e8e47c459cbd81fd59becca1e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The caravan must reach its destination …………………………… sunset.",
            "description": "We use before to indicate time we use in front of to indicate position.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "before",
                "in front of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2fccdaad97544d098b6df94607aabe89"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will return ……………………….. an hour.",
            "description": "We use in before a noun denoting a period of time",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "74c9c6a4f3da4697a422cb1b0da51bf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must start …………………….. dawn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "348a93504b5c46659b11e510a69eee4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been waiting for this moment …………………….. years.",
            "description": "We use for to indicate duration.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b541d74d793c42fb8184a948b25dd7b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………… the top of the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9305c84a83064989894fdfe03bafe4c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is the boy I was speaking ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "386eb6f17b4248768de931b15d8cd67f"
        }
    ]
}